articlesfreedom.com 2010-06-29

# Privacy Policy | ArticlesFreedom.com

**General**. ArticlesFreedom places great importance in protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy is designed to explain the manner in which ArticlesFreedom collects, uses, and discloses the personal information provided by you as a result of the use of ArticlesFreedom's Web Site and the content, information and services provided through the Web Site by ArticlesFreedom.

**Users' Consent**. BY ACCESSING THIS WEB SITE, THE WEB SITE LOCATED AT THE URL WWW.ArticlesFreedom.com AND/OR ANY OTHER SITE PROVIDED BY ArticlesFreedom (COLLECTIVELY, THE "SITE"), YOU ARE SIGNIFYING, EXPRESSING AND PROVIDING YOUR CONSENT TO THE INFORMATION COLLECTION, INFORMATION USAGE, AND OTHER PROCEDURES DESCRIBED IN THE PRIVACY POLICY BELOW. ArticlesFreedom reserves the right to change this policy at any time, without notice, by posting a new privacy policy at this location. The collection, use and disclosure of your personal information by ArticlesFreedom will be governed by the version of this Policy in effect at that time. Please check this page periodically for any changes. Please [**contact us**](http://www.articlesfreedom.com/help/contact-us) if you have any questions about our privacy policy.

**Collection and Use of Information**. In order for you to access certain materials or pages (i.e. author signup, tell a friend, and the like) and to register as a user on this Site, this Site requires that you provide certain personal information, including, but not limited to, your name, phone number and e-mail address. We use this information in order to contact you to provide you with further information about our company and services, as well as for other commercial and/or internal purposes such as market research in order to better understand the demographics of our Site visitors and potential customers and partners. We may share this information with our authorized partners and/or with third parties who act for or on behalf of us, but we do not otherwise provide or sell any information gathered on this Site to outside vendors.

**User Tracking**. This Site implements a user tracking feature, whereby the activities of each unique visitor to the Site are monitored. This is done regardless of whether the visitor has registered on the Site or is visiting the Site anonymously. If you do not register on this Site or fill in your personal details on any forms, you do remain anonymous and we do not discover your identity. If you do register on this Site, our use of user tracking enables us to identify your future and prior activities on the Site, including your activity before you registered. This includes pages on our Site that you visited. The purpose of our user tracking is to analyze our visitors' actions in order to improve the user experience of visitors to our Site, as well as to better understand the priorities and interests of our potential customers and partners in order to better suit their needs and increase the efficiency of our sales and marketing processes.

**Use of Cookies**. A "cookie" is a small text file transferred by a Web Site to a computer that is browsing the Web Site. However ArticlesFreedom doesnot use cookies to track you! 

**Internet Protocol Addresses**. We collect the IP addresses of all visitors to our Site. We use your IP address in order to administer the Site, help diagnose problems with our server, to gather broad demographic information, and for the "User Tracking" described above.

**Hyperlinks**. This Site contains hyperlinks to other web sites. This privacy policy applies only to this Site and not to any other sites, including sites accessed by hyperlink from this Site. ArticlesFreedom has no responsibility, liability for, or control over those other web sites or Internet resources or their collection, use and disclosure of your personal information, nor has it any control over the privacy policies of any of these sites. When you leave the ArticleFreedom Site via one of the links then you should read the privacy policy, if any, provided by the site that you have visited.

In order to assist in protecting the confidentiality of your personal information, ArticlesFreedom applies security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. However, in light of the nature of Internet technologies, security and privacy risks cannot be eliminated and, therefore, ArticlesFreedom cannot guarantee that your personal information will not be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Policy.

**3rd Party Based Advertising**.  

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on ArticlesFreedom.com.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet.
  * You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
